同時具備無辜和明白，
Innocence and clarity in one,
這份純真僅僅是少數
purity is only found in some
不曉得所謂口蜜腹劍，
Lack of words in trickery or harm,
僅能在心的底部發現
only from the bottom of the heart
在寓言中學到
Learned it in a parable
在歌謠中聽到
Found it in a lullaby
曾經有人提過它
Someone said it long ago
夜裡你也想過它
Dreamed it on a sleepless night
你能聽到那聲音
You can hear it whispering
前提是你要聆聽
only if you're listening
在你美好的回憶裡
Searching all your favored memories
同時具備無辜和明白，
Innocence and clarity in one,
這份純真僅僅是少數
purity is only found in some
不曉得所謂口蜜腹劍，
Lack of words in trickery or harm,
僅能在心的底部發現
only from the bottom of the heart
爬過山坡到那裡
Far beyond the mountainside
自己親眼看一次
Take a gander of your own
再靠近點河中心
Nearer to the river's eyes
場景就已如此美
Beauty in the scene alone
我會在那好好等
I'll be waiting reverently
就在蘋果樹之下
Underneath the apple tree
深思著大家的使命
Pondering on what we're all to be
同時具備無辜和明白，
Innocence and clarity in one,
這份純真僅僅是少數
purity is only found in some
不曉得所謂口蜜腹劍，
Lack of words in trickery or harm,
僅能在心的底部發現
only from the bottom of the heart
Only from the bottom of the heart
僅能在心的底部發現